inspectionsupport.net 2018-08-14

# Privacy Policy | Inspection Support Network

Inspection Support Limited Liability Company (“Inspection Support”, or “we”, “us”, or “our”, as applicable) values the privacy of our website visitors, system users, and commercial partners. Inspection Support respects your privacy and is committed to using responsible practices in the collection, maintenance, and use of your personal information. This Privacy Policy, as modified from time to time, describes our practices in connection with information collected through our inspectionsupport.net website (together with all subdomains and related websites, and together with related mobile device applications, the “the Website”)

As a general principle, information you provide to us will only be used or shared by Inspection Support as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

 **By visiting or using the Website, you agree to the practices and policies set forth in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Website.**

* #### Information We Collect

We may collect two basic types of information from you in conjunction with your use of the Website – personal information and non-personal information. **“Personal information”** is any information that can individually identify you and includes, for example and without limitation, your name, email address, username, telephone number, postal address, and so forth. **“Non-personal information”** includes information that does not personally identify you, but may include (without limitation) tracking and usage information about your location, demographics, transaction information, use of the Website and the Internet, etc.

##### Personal Information

There are a number of circumstances in which you may voluntarily supply us with your personal information. The following lists the most common ways in which we may collect your personal information:

  * Sign up to receive information or related services from us
  * Registration for an account on the Website to enable you to use Website functions, such as utilizing  
Inspection Support Network features and functions
  * Participation on social media accounts involving Inspection Support
  * Any other place on the Website where you knowingly volunteer personal information

##### Children’s Online Privacy

Inspection Support respects the privacy of children and we are committed to complying with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We do not intentionally collect personal information from children. If we learn that a child under 13 has provided personal information to us without verification of parental consent, we will take commercially reasonable steps to delete that information.

##### Social Media Sites

When you interact with a Inspection Support account on a social media platform, such as Facebook, Twitter, or YouTube, we may collect the personal information that you make available to us on that page or account, including your user ID and/or user name, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media service. Please note, however, that we will comply with the privacy policies of the corresponding social media platform and we will only collect and store such personal information that we are permitted to collect by these social media platforms.

Our Website may include social media widgets, such as Facebook, YouTube, and Twitter widgets. These features may collect information about your IP address and which page you’re visiting on our Website, and they may set a cookie to make sure their feature functions properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. Your interactions with those features are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.

##### Non-Personal Information

When you use the Website, our servers may keep an activity log that does not identify you individually. These logs may include information such as device information about your computer, mobile device, or other device that you use to access the Website, which may include your IP address, browser, etc., and additional traffic data, such as time and date of access, access times, and referring website addresses. We use this information to assist us in running the Website and ensuring proper operation.

##### Use of Cookies

When you interact with the Website, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, “cookie” information, and the page you requested.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies, you may not have access to certain features, content, or personalization available through the Website.

##### “Do Not Track” Practices

At this time, we do not honor do-not-track signals from browsers or other consumer choice mechanisms regarding the collection of behavioral tracking data. While we collect personal information from you as described above, we do not collect personal information from you to monitor your online activities across third party websites or online services and over time (also known as behavioral advertising or interest-based advertising). We do not use or allow third parties to collect personal information from you on the Website in order to monitor your online activities across third party websites or online services and over time.

##### Email and Other Communications

We may contact you by email or other means at an email address that you have provided to us. For example, we may send you promotional offers or our newsletter. If you do not want to receive email from us, please let us know through the “unsubscribe” feature included in our communications.

* #### Our Use of Information

We use the information we collect from you and about you to help us personalize and continually improve your experience with the Website. As non-limiting examples, we may use the information we collect from and about you in the following ways:

  * Provide you with the products and services you request from us, such as access to the features of  
the Inspection Support Network
  * Communicate with you about your account with us or your use of the Website, and send you information  
about features on the Website
  * Communicate with you about changes to our policies
  * Personalize content and experiences on our Website
  * Collect fees for use of the Website
  * Share your personal information with others you may be interacting with through the Website
  * Send you newsletters, offers, or special events by email or other media
  * Optimize or improve our products, services, and operations
  * Detect, investigate, or prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal

* #### Our Disclosure of Information

We will only share personal information as provided in this Privacy Policy, and within our company and corporate affiliates.

We may make your information available to certain third party service providers, such as contractors, agents, or sponsors, who help us manage or provide services offered on our Website, such as hosting, analytics, customer service, etc.

We may also use or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to applicable law or comply with legal process served on us or the Website; (b) respond to requests from public and government authorities; (c) protect and defend our rights or property, the Website, or our users; and (d) act under emergency circumstances to protect the personal safety of us, our affiliates, agents, or the users of the Website or the public.

##### Merger, Sale, Or Bankruptcy

If we sell all or part of our business, or make a sale or transfer of our assets, or are otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of our business, or are involved in a bankruptcy, Inspection Support may transfer your information to the party or parties involved as part of that transaction.

##### California Disclosures

If you are a California resident and have an established business relationship with us, you can request a notice disclosing the categories of personal information we have shared with third parties, for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes, during the preceding calendar year. To request a notice, please submit your request to Inspection Support at help@inspectionsupport.net.

* #### Security

We are concerned about ensuring the security of your personal information. We use commercially reasonable efforts to protect your personal information collected through the Website from access, loss, misuse, alteration, or destruction by any unauthorized party. Please understand, however, that no transmission of data over the internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. You are also responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse such as by maintaining the confidentiality of your username and password, and logging out of your account when not using the Website.

* #### Links To or From Other Sites

Please note that the Website may link to other websites and online services operated by third parties. These websites and applications operate independently from us, and we do not control their privacy policies, which may be different from ours. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party websites or applications.

* #### Notice to Non-U.S. Users

As the Internet is a global environment, collecting and processing personal information may involve the transmission of this data internationally, including into and/or outside of the United States. Therefore, by communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to your personal data being processed in this way.

Specifically, if you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that by using the Website, your personal information may be transferred to the United States, the privacy laws of which may be deemed by your country to have inadequate data protection. If you are located outside of the United States and voluntarily submit personal information to us, you thereby consent to the general use of such information as provided in this Privacy Policy and to the transfer of that information to, and/or storage of that information in, the United States. Nevertheless, our Website is intended for users only within the United States.

* #### Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time in our sole discretion, and will post and maintain the most recent version of the Privacy Policy on the Website. We may not notify Website visitors of any such amendments by e-mail or other personal contact.  You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Policy upon each visit to the Website. You can determine if the Privacy Policy has been revised since your last visit by referring to the “Last Modified” date at the top of this document.

* #### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or its implementation, please contact:

Email: [help@inspectionsupport.net](mailto:help@inspectionsupport.net)

Toll-free: (800) 700 8112
